kumarrishabh7631@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rishabh-choudhary-701743181

SUMMARY

A Computer Science major with a strong passion to create. Being an avid team player and leader for various groups at the institute, focus on academics and mix of extra-curricular activities, I am keen on working with a process-driven organization to add value. I have developed skills in the field of computer science during the last few years in freelancing and I am sure to work with the vision of the organization to steer it to a market leadership position Expertise: React, php, js, mysqli, CSS, HTML, bootstrap, figma

EXPERIENCE

React Developer

Hoicko March 2022 - Present

Full-stack Developer

Fiverr Freelancers (Buyer and Seller)

July 2020 - May 2022

EDUCATION

Govt. Engineering College Bikaner

B.TECH ,

2018 - 2022

SKILLS

- PHP
- MySQL
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- JavaScript
- HTML5
- Bootstrap
- SQL
- Databases
- React.js
- jQuery

CONTACT DETAILS

Phone No.:

(Personal Number)

Email: kumarrishabh7631@gmail.com

Address: Udaipur, Rajasthan, India